Magdalena Stanek

Senior Asset Analyst - Hewlett Packard Enterprise

Shelby Twp, MI - Email me on Indeed: indeed.com/r/Magdalena-Stanek/32bf3720b2e7b2f2

I am a highly motivated and qualified IT Professional with 9 years of industry experience. I am aiming to use my proven technical, management, and communication skills to find a challenging position in which I could grow professionally.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Senior Asset Analyst

Hewlett Packard Enterprise - 2010 to Present

Supported multiple accounts (Private and Public sectors)

- Managed maintenance renewals which included obtaining and verifying quotes, obtaining PO and maintenance certificate information, reviewing invoices, packing slips and searching for data in various tools to verify accuracy of information
- Worked with Finance department and vendors to resolve payment discrepancies
- Participated in highly visible projects such as network inventories and audits
- · Analyzed large amounts of data using Excel frequent usage of Pivot tables, V-lookup and other functions
- Lead Analyst on Bristol-Myers account
- trained and monitored off-shore team members while managing day to day activities
- regularly compared records to scanning tools (SCCM and Airwatch), analyzed data and worked with site technicians to resolve discrepancies/make updates
- audited forms and process documents for audit and retention purposes
- updated and distributed Dashboard to all global sites, met regularly with the client to discuss the findings
- monitored and granted access to the SharePoint
- Created new and improved existing processes
- Generated ad hoc reports for clients and management
- Managed Escalations: identified potential escalations and alerted management proactively
- Conducted extensive research on assets in database for billing accuracy
- · Researched and created software records in Asset Manager
- Researched/analyzed records in various systems and ensured that proper updates were made
- · Created/modified hardware records in Asset Manager both manually and through LDSS updates
- Worked with Hewlett Packard Financial Services (HPFS), Technology Services (TS), Logistics, Procurement representatives to obtain information and make updates in different tools collecting serial numbers, locations, and project information data
- Balanced internal needs with customers' needs within defined parameters
- · Proactively and reactively provided solutions to prevent problems from occurring in areas of responsibility
- Worked as part of a team often virtual, global and multi-functional.
- Worked closely with project management and personnel to finalize reports and ensure timely delivery
- Updated and provided metrics to management
- Utilized SAP tool to dispatch technicians to client's sites to pick up equipment

IT Asset Analyst

Hewlett Packard Enterprise - Pontiac, MI - 2007 to Present

Procurement Analyst

Hewlett Packard Enterprise - 2007 to 2010

Facilitated the purchasing process between Project Managers and Supply Chain for purchase of hardware, software, maintenance and services (Kraft account)

- Investigated and resolved issues during the procurement process
- Responsible for reviewing BOMs, SOWs, quotes, POs, packing slips and invoices
- Managed maintenance contracts by processing yearly renewals, and adding/removing items from maintenance on monthly bases.
- Managed multiple blank Purchase Orders
- Created 200+ quotes in Cisco tool for yearly maintenance renewal
- · Processed invoices for payment
- · Receipt acknowledged in CAS (Corporate Administration System) to ensure timely invoice payments
- Performed Goods Receipt and created Asset Records in SAP

EDUCATION

MBA in Finance and International Business

Oakland University - Rochester, MI September 2014 to December 2016

Bachelor in Accounting

Baker College - Auburn Hills, MI May 2004 to December 2007

SKILLS

Excell (9 years), Asset Management (7 years), Vendor Management (9 years), Communications (9 years)

AWARDS

Beta Gamma Sigma

February 2017

Beta Gamma Sigma - honor society, awarded to me for being in top 20% of my graduate MBA program.

ADDITIONAL INFORMATION

SKILLS AND ATTRIBUTES:

- IT Hardware Asset Management Auditing and Analysis
- Hardware maintenance renewals
- Project management
- Procurement
- Vendor management
- Service Delivery
- Outstanding training skills
- Strong follow up skills
- · Able to multitask, detail oriented and well organized
- · Outstanding analytical and problem solving skills
- Works well under pressure in fast-paced environment
- · Exceptional interpersonal skills
- Able to handle multiple projects at the same time and meet critical deadlines
- Interacts professionally with all levels of staff and maintains the highest level of confidentiality

COMPUTER SKILLS:

Microsoft Word, Microsoft Excel, PowerPoint, Outlook Express, Access, Internet Explorer.

COMPUTER TOOLS and SYSTEMS:

SAP, Corporate Administration System (CAS), Asset Center, Asset Manager, ESL, Vitalize, AVS, Airwatch, CMBD+, Dottools, CAMS, SharePoint, Asset Edge, Virtual Warehouse, Service Request Tools, Sandy, Aries/ Aldea, RevGen, SmartBuy.